Finding Aid for Nisbett Family papers, 1892-1923
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Nisbett Family papers 1892-1923
Nisbett Family.
1 linear foot
852118 Aa 2
Big Rapids, Michigan family. Correspondence and other papers concerning Big Rapids (Mich.) Post Office, Big Rapids Board of Trade, and family matters; also photographs.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of family members (donor no. 4175 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
The Nisbett family were residents of Big Rapids, Michigan. One family member, William P. Nisbett was secretary of the Big Rapids Board of Trade.
The collection consists of correspondence and other papers relating to family matters and to the activities of William P. Nisbett with the Big Rapids (Mich.) Post Office, Big Rapids Board of Trade, and the National Wagon Company.
Subjects:
Big Rapids (Mich.); Big Rapids Board of Trade.; Boards of trade--Michigan--Big Rapids.; Ferris Institute.; Manufactures--Michigan--Big Rapids.; Nesbitt family.; Pontiac (Mich.); Postal service.; Governors--Michigan.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Nisbett, William P., b. 1847.
Contributors:
Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.; National Wagon Company (Big Rapids, Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Correspondence and other papers
  - Undated, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - January 1892-December 1895 (Box 1)
  - January 1896-December 1898 (Box 1)
  - January-June 1899 (Box 1)
  - July-December 1899 (Box 1)
  - January-April 1900 (Box 1)
  - May-July 1900 (Box 1)
  - August-December 1900 (Box 1)
  - January-April 1901 (Box 1)
  - May-August 1901 (Box 1)
  - September-December 1901 (Box 1)
  - January-June 1902 (Box 1)
  - July-December 1902 (Box 1)
  - January-April 1903 (Box 1)
  - May-August 1903 (Box 1)
  - September-December 1903 (Box 1)
  - 1904 (Box 1)
  - January-April 1905 (Box 1)
  - May-August 1905 (Box 1)
  - September-December 1905 (Box 1)
  - January-February 1906 (Box 1)
  - March-May 1906 (Box 1)
  - June-December 1906 (Box 1)
  - 1907-1914 (Box 1)
  - 1915 (Box 1)
  - 1916-1923 (Box 1)
- William P. Nisbett
  - "Personal reminiscences of Pontiac, Mich. in the 1860s and 1870s" undated, 19 p. (Box 1)
  - Diary, undated (Box 1)
  - Letterbook, undated (Box 1)
  - Big Rapids Board of Trade papers (Box 1)
- National Wagon Company, Big Rapids
  - Directors and stockholders meetings, 1904-1905, 1 volume (Box 1)
  - Time Book, 1904-1905 (Box 1)
  - Ledgers, 1904-1905 (Box 1)
- Photographs
  - Portraits of William P. Nisbett (Box 1)